<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Places on The Emerald Semaphore of Keta-9</title>
    <link>https://example.org/categories/places/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Places on The Emerald Semaphore of Keta-9</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/categories/places/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Glassloop Archives</title>
      <link>https://example.org/places/glassloop-archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/places/glassloop-archives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Glassloop Archives&lt;/strong&gt; are an abandoned data preservation complex appearing in &lt;em&gt;The Emerald Semaphore of Keta-9&lt;/em&gt;. The facility serves as the primary workplace of &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/rohane-voss&#34;&gt;Rohane Voss&lt;/a&gt;, where he begins his investigation into the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/keta-9-semaphore-entity&#34;&gt;Keta-9 Semaphore&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Located within the upper framework of &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/orbital-relay-keta-9&#34;&gt;Orbital Relay Keta-9&lt;/a&gt;, the Archives were originally designed to house analog backups of early comm-protocols and transmission blueprints. Over time, the institution became a labyrinthine collection of obsolete systems, with corridors lined by glass-encased servers and lightducts refracting residual green illumination.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halvorsen’s Drift</title>
      <link>https://example.org/places/halvorsen-drift/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/places/halvorsen-drift/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Halvorsen’s Drift&lt;/strong&gt; is a decaying industrial sector on the periphery of &lt;em&gt;Orbital Relay Keta-9&lt;/em&gt; and a key location in &lt;em&gt;The Emerald Semaphore of Keta-9&lt;/em&gt;. The area is a cluster of broken tether rings and repurposed maintenance tunnels, named after early relay designer &lt;strong&gt;Orren Halvorsen&lt;/strong&gt;, whose designs formed the basis for the first wave of orbital communication systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/cassian-merek&#34;&gt; Cassian Merek &lt;/a&gt; operates from a workshop hidden within the Drift, salvaging obsolete relay nodes and broadcasting equipment. The site serves as his base of operations and one of the few unmonitored zones beyond &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/director-halver&#34;&gt;Director Halver&lt;/a&gt;’s surveillance range.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Meridian Dockyard</title>
      <link>https://example.org/places/meridian-dockyard/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/places/meridian-dockyard/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Meridian Dockyard&lt;/strong&gt; is an orbital industrial hub featured in &lt;em&gt;The Emerald Semaphore of Keta-9&lt;/em&gt;. It serves as the primary salvage and repair station for decommissioned relay equipment, where &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/cassian-merek&#34;&gt;Cassian Merek&lt;/a&gt; operates his workshop.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Located along the outer ring of &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/orbital-relay-keta-9&#34;&gt;Orbital Relay Keta-9&lt;/a&gt;, the dockyard is a sprawling network of floating platforms, docking clamps, and maintenance bays. It is primarily automated, with slow-moving cranes and robotic tethers handling heavy payloads.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;function&#34;&gt;Function&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Meridian Dockyard specializes in the disassembly, repurposing, and storage of obsolete comm-nodes, antennae, and relay nodes. It also houses temporary living quarters for salvage crews, providing basic life support and minimal shielding against orbital debris.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Orbital Relay Keta-9</title>
      <link>https://example.org/places/orbital-relay-keta-9/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/places/orbital-relay-keta-9/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Orbital Relay Keta-9&lt;/strong&gt; is the primary setting of &lt;em&gt;The Emerald Semaphore of Keta-9&lt;/em&gt;. It is a massive derelict communication structure orbiting just above the exosphere, once used for long-range interlink between Earth’s upper cities and outer relay networks.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Once a vital node in the planetary communication grid, the station fell into partial decay following the collapse of the relay consortium. Now partially automated and structurally unstable, Keta-9 serves as both a physical and symbolic graveyard of forgotten messages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Subsignal Corridors</title>
      <link>https://example.org/places/subsignal-corridors/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/places/subsignal-corridors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;The Subsignal Corridors&lt;/strong&gt; are an extensive network of service tunnels within &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/orbital-relay-keta-9&#34;&gt;Orbital Relay Keta-9&lt;/a&gt;. They serve as the hidden pathways connecting the lower and upper sectors of the relay, providing access to obsolete maintenance systems.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These corridors are named for their original function of routing secondary or redundant signal lines. Over time, they became largely abandoned, retaining only faint electrical hums and sporadic pulse flashes from residual activity.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;function&#34;&gt;Function&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The corridors are used by &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/rohane-voss&#34;&gt;Rohane Voss&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/cassian-merek&#34;&gt;Cassian Merek&lt;/a&gt; to navigate the relay unnoticed. They are also where the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/relay-choir&#34;&gt;Relay Choir&lt;/a&gt; is first encountered, as their harmonic pulses resonate along the narrow passageways, amplifying signal anomalies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
