<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Characters on Klyth-77 — The Halcyon Codex of Sarn</title>
    <link>https://example.org/categories/characters/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Characters on Klyth-77 — The Halcyon Codex of Sarn</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://example.org/categories/characters/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Orrin Kael</title>
      <link>https://example.org/characters/orrin-kael/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 22 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/characters/orrin-kael/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Orrin Kael is an operative in the city of &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; known for navigating the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt; and monitoring anomalies linked to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;. His work bridges the gap between the city’s physical architecture and the cryptic information in the Codex.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Kael was trained in urban reconnaissance and structural analysis. Early assignments in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/loom-arrondissement&#34;&gt;Loom-Arrondissement&lt;/a&gt; gave him extensive knowledge of Sarn’s vertical infrastructure, making him a key resource for interpreting unexpected shifts reported by the Codex.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Scribe</title>
      <link>https://example.org/characters/the-scribe/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/characters/the-scribe/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Scribe is an enigmatic figure whose annotations in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt; guide the actions of &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/lysander-veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/characters/eira-voss&#34;&gt;Eira Voss&lt;/a&gt;. Their identity and motives remain largely unexplored, creating intrigue throughout the narrative.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Little is known about The Scribe beyond the marginalia left in the Codex. Analysis of writing style and patterns suggests extensive familiarity with the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; and its subterranean networks, including the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Scribe&amp;rsquo;s contributions appear indirectly, as guidance embedded within the Codex. These annotations often anticipate structural or social anomalies and challenge protagonists to interpret them accurately.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Dr. Allene Mire</title>
      <link>https://example.org/characters/dr-allene-mire/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 18 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/characters/dr-allene-mire/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Dr. Allene Mire is a leading biologist in the city of &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; who becomes involved in the investigations surrounding the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;. Her expertise in genetic mapping and social stratification informs many of the debates about the Codex&amp;rsquo;s implications.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Mire&amp;rsquo;s research in cellular genetics and the documentation of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.org/others/vellum-names&#34;&gt;Vellum Names&lt;/a&gt; system earned her recognition within Sarn&amp;rsquo;s scientific circles. She has a reputation for rigorous methodology and a cautious approach to anomalies reported in the Codex.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Eira Voss</title>
      <link>https://example.org/characters/eira-voss/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/characters/eira-voss/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Eira Voss is a prominent engineer specializing in reflective systems within the &lt;a href=&#34;places/City-of-Sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;. She works closely with &lt;a href=&#34;characters/Lysander-Veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt; to understand the interactions between the &lt;a href=&#34;others/Halcyon-Codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt; and the city&amp;rsquo;s structures.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Voss was trained in the mechanics and engineering of the &lt;a href=&#34;places/Loom-Arrondissement&#34;&gt;Loom Arrondissement&lt;/a&gt;. Her early work in architectural simulations led her to the study of the Codex, recognizing its patterns within the city&amp;rsquo;s vertical layouts.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Eira assists Lysander Veyr in interpreting the Codex, often focusing on the physical and structural effects it seems to impose on Sarn. She conducts experiments in the &lt;a href=&#34;places/Tenebrous-Runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt; to verify anomalies reported in the manuscripts and cross-references her findings with the &lt;a href=&#34;others/Klyth-Index&#34;&gt;Klyth Index&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lysander Veyr</title>
      <link>https://example.org/characters/lysander-veyr/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/characters/lysander-veyr/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lysander Veyr is the central protagonist in &lt;em&gt;Klyth-77 The Halcyon Codex of Sarn&lt;/em&gt;. He is an archivist and mapkeeper of the city of &lt;a href=&#34;places/City-of-Sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; and becomes deeply involved with the mysteries of the &lt;a href=&#34;others/Halcyon-Codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;background&#34;&gt;Background&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Veyr grew up within the &lt;a href=&#34;places/Loom-Arrondissement&#34;&gt;Loom Arrondissement&lt;/a&gt;, studying the complex vertical structures of Sarn. He is known for his meticulous attention to the indexing of the &lt;a href=&#34;others/Klyth-Index&#34;&gt;Klyth Index&lt;/a&gt; and his ability to interpret marginal annotations in ancient manuscripts.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
