<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Others on Klyth-77 — The Halcyon Codex of Sarn</title>
    <link>https://klyth77.com/others/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Others on Klyth-77 — The Halcyon Codex of Sarn</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://klyth77.com/others/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Vellum Names</title>
      <link>https://klyth77.com/others/vellum-names/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://klyth77.com/others/vellum-names/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vellum Names are a system of coded annotations found within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt; and related archival materials. They record social, genetic, and functional attributes of inhabitants and locations within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;composition-and-structure&#34;&gt;Composition and Structure&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Each Vellum Name consists of a unique identifier, marginal notes, and occasionally symbolic diagrams. These entries are indexed through the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/klyth-index&#34;&gt;Klyth Index&lt;/a&gt; to allow researchers and archivists to cross-reference individuals, locations, and Codex annotations.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Vellum Names provide critical context for understanding the interactions between characters, the city, and the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;. They guide &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/lysander-veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/eira-voss&#34;&gt;Eira Voss&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/dr-allene-mire&#34;&gt;Dr. Allene Mire&lt;/a&gt; in their analysis of Sarn’s architecture and social hierarchies.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obscura Press Archives</title>
      <link>https://klyth77.com/others/obscura-press-archives/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://klyth77.com/others/obscura-press-archives/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Obscura Press Archives house records, limited print runs, and documentation related to the publication and distribution of manuscripts, including the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;. The archives are located within a secure facility in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;composition-and-structure&#34;&gt;Composition and Structure&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The archives contain cataloged editions, scanned fragments, and reference materials. They include the indexing system of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/klyth-index&#34;&gt;Klyth Index&lt;/a&gt; and maintain copies of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/vellum-names&#34;&gt;Vellum Names&lt;/a&gt; records.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Characters such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/lysander-veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/eira-voss&#34;&gt;Eira Voss&lt;/a&gt; consult the archives to verify Codex entries and trace historical annotations. The facility provides access to rare fragments and reference data critical to their investigations.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lightduct Mirrors</title>
      <link>https://klyth77.com/others/lightduct-mirrors/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 12 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://klyth77.com/others/lightduct-mirrors/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Lightduct Mirrors are engineered reflective surfaces used throughout the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; to channel and direct sunlight across different layers. They play a key role in environmental management and architectural design.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;function-and-design&#34;&gt;Function and Design&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These mirrors are strategically placed to optimize illumination in residential and research districts. Their orientation and angles are carefully calculated to maintain consistent light flow across vertical corridors and open spaces.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;While not directly interacted with by the main characters, Lightduct Mirrors influence the city environment, impacting visibility and perception in areas like the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/loom-arrondissement&#34;&gt;Loom-Arrondissement&lt;/a&gt; and upper residential platforms.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Klyth Index</title>
      <link>https://klyth77.com/others/klyth-index/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://klyth77.com/others/klyth-index/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Klyth Index is a cataloging system that indexes the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt; entries and associated city phenomena. It provides structured references for researchers and archivists within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;composition-and-structure&#34;&gt;Composition and Structure&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Index assigns unique identifiers to Codex annotations, including references to structural shifts, &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/vellum-names&#34;&gt;Vellum Names&lt;/a&gt;, and specific locations within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt;. It serves as a cross-referencing tool for navigating complex data.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Klyth Index aids characters such as &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/lysander-veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/eira-voss&#34;&gt;Eira Voss&lt;/a&gt; in interpreting the Codex. It functions as both a practical guide and a symbolic framework for understanding Sarn’s layered architecture.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Halcyon Codex</title>
      <link>https://klyth77.com/others/halcyon-codex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 08 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://klyth77.com/others/halcyon-codex/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Halcyon Codex is an annotated manuscript linked to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; that records cryptic information and structural anomalies. It is studied closely by &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/lysander-veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/eira-voss&#34;&gt;Eira Voss&lt;/a&gt;, and &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/characters/dr-allene-mire&#34;&gt;Dr. Allene Mire&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;composition-and-structure&#34;&gt;Composition and Structure&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Codex contains text, diagrams, and marginalia that reference the city’s architecture and social hierarchy. Embedded within its pages are the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/others/vellum-names&#34;&gt;Vellum Names&lt;/a&gt;, a system used to denote social and genetic attributes of inhabitants.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;role-in-the-story&#34;&gt;Role in the Story&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Codex drives the narrative by revealing anomalies and guiding characters through both literal and metaphorical passages in Sarn. It interacts with the city’s architecture, prompting shifts in corridors and influencing events in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://klyth77.com/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
