<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Places on Klyth-77 — The Halcyon Codex of Sarn</title>
    <link>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/categories/places/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Places on Klyth-77 — The Halcyon Codex of Sarn</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/categories/places/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Whistled Avenues</title>
      <link>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/whistled-avenues/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/whistled-avenues/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Whistled Avenues are upper-level streets in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt; characterized by open spaces and the flow of natural light through engineered channels. They form part of the city’s residential and social zones.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;geography-and-architecture&#34;&gt;Geography and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These avenues are elevated, wide, and lined with structures optimized for sunlight exposure. The architecture emphasizes openness and air circulation, creating subtle acoustic effects as wind moves through the upper levels.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;society-and-culture&#34;&gt;Society and Culture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Residents and visitors of the Whistled Avenues engage in communal and recreational activities. The spaces serve as marketplaces, meeting points, and observation areas, maintaining a cultural rhythm distinct from the industrial and research districts below.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Tenebrous Runnels</title>
      <link>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/tenebrous-runnels/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/tenebrous-runnels/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Tenebrous Runnels are a labyrinthine network of subterranean tunnels beneath the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;. They connect the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/lower-foundries&#34;&gt;Lower Foundries&lt;/a&gt; to upper districts and provide secretive passageways utilized by key characters, including &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/characters/orrin-kael&#34;&gt;Orrin Kael&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;geography-and-architecture&#34;&gt;Geography and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;These tunnels are narrow, winding, and partially unstable, with interlocking chambers and maintenance corridors. Their complexity is both practical and symbolic, serving as hidden arteries through the city that mirror the coded information in the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Lower Foundries</title>
      <link>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/lower-foundries/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/lower-foundries/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Lower Foundries form the industrial base of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;, containing manufacturing plants, maintenance hubs, and utility networks. The district supports the upper layers by providing essential resources and access to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;geography-and-architecture&#34;&gt;Geography and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Foundries consist of expansive chambers, conveyor networks, and service tunnels. Vertical shafts connect this industrial layer to residential and research districts above, facilitating transportation and the movement of materials throughout the city.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Loom-Arrondissement</title>
      <link>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/loom-arrondissement/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/loom-arrondissement/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The Loom-Arrondissement is a central district within the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/city-of-sarn&#34;&gt;City of Sarn&lt;/a&gt;, known for its dense architectural layering and concentration of research and engineering activities. It serves as a hub for the study and application of the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;geography-and-architecture&#34;&gt;Geography and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;This district features interconnected platforms, vertical corridors, and observation decks. It is designed for both habitation and experimentation, allowing engineers like &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/characters/eira-voss&#34;&gt;Eira Voss&lt;/a&gt; to conduct structural simulations and archival operations alongside &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/characters/lysander-veyr&#34;&gt;Lysander Veyr&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>City of Sarn</title>
      <link>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/city-of-sarn/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 25 Jun 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/city-of-sarn/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;overview&#34;&gt;Overview&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The City of Sarn is a vertically structured metropolis with multiple layers of habitation, industrial zones, and service channels, including the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/loom-arrondissement&#34;&gt;Loom-Arrondissement&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt;. The city serves as the primary setting for events connected to the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/others/halcyon-codex&#34;&gt;Halcyon Codex&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h2 id=&#34;geography-and-architecture&#34;&gt;Geography and Architecture&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Sarn is designed with layered levels, each serving distinct functions. The &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/lower-foundries&#34;&gt;Lower Foundries&lt;/a&gt; manage industrial production, while upper districts incorporate light-management technologies and residential areas. Complex corridors and service tunnels, such as the &lt;a href=&#34;https://moviemania.ihtl.fr/places/tenebrous-runnels&#34;&gt;Tenebrous Runnels&lt;/a&gt;, link the layers and facilitate both movement and hidden passages.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
